A Guide to the Elizabeth Archer Barnard Nickels Papers, 1941-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Project Files, 1941-1990. (Box 22-25, Folder 1-93)
  - Subseries IV.D. - Miscellaneous and unidentified firms.
    - Medical offices, Frederick Hyland AIA, Architect, 206-208 East Clay Street, Richmond, Virginia, 1961. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 55)
    - Residence, Charles Shiflett & Thomas A. Gresham, Architects, 605 West Cary Street, Richmond, Virginia, 1961. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 56)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, Appomattox Street, Hopewell, Virginia, 1961. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 57)
    - La Vogue Incoporated, Virginia Elevator Company, 5th & Gray Streets, Richmond, Virginia, 1962. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 58)
    - Residence, Frederick Hyland AIA, Architect, unidentified location, 1962. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 59)
    - The Tides Inn, Chesapeake Club, Virginia Elevator Company, Irvington, Virginia, 1963. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 60)
    - Merchants Hope Church, Rawlings & Wilson Architects, Prince George County, Virginia, 1963-1990. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 61)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, 200 Virginia Avenue, Richmond, Virginia, 1965. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 62)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, Telegraph Road, Henrico County, Virginia, 1965. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 63)
    - Leigh Haven, West End Builders, drawn by HCL, Pinedale Farms, Richmond, Virginia, 1966. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 64)
    - Proposed fertilizer lab, unidentified firm, unidentified location, 1966. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 65)
    - Residence, unknown firm, Locke Lane, Richmond, Virginia, 1966. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 66)
    - Mobil Chemical Company, proposed lab and office, Carneal & Johnston, Architects, Hanover County, Virginia, 1966. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 67)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, Mansion Drive, Hopewell, Virginia, 1968. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 68)
    - Residence, Earl M. Childrey, Inc. General Contractor, 4603 Wythe Avenue, Richmond, Virginia, 1969. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 69)
    - Comstock, Dunston & Conjurers Neck, unidentified firm, Colonial Heights, Virginia, 1969. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 70)
    - Preliminary studies of Comstock, Dunston & Conjurers Neck, unidentified firm, Colonial Heights, Virginia, 1969 (rolled). (Box 24)
    - Suveys, Austin Brockenbrough & Associates, unidentified location, 1970. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 71)
    - Proposed office and laboratory, unidentified firm, unidentified location, 1970-1972. (Map-case 8, Drawer 14, Folder 72)
    - Residence for Mrs. Beth Nickels, unidentified firm, unidentified location, 1973. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 73)
    - Studies for Sabet Hills & Hidden Hills, unidentified firm, Prince George County, Virginia, 1975. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 74)
    - Studies for Sabet Hills & Hidden Hills, unidentified firm, Prince George County, Virginia, 1975. (Box 25)
    - Residence, Hedgelawn, David T. Evans, unidentified location, 1986. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 75)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, 714 S. Meadow Street, Richmond, Virginia, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 76)
    - Residence, H. Clarke Linkous Contractor, 5508 Bewdly Road, Richmond, Virginia, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 77)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, Chesterfield, Virginia, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 78)
    - Residence, unidentified firm, Kippax & Riverside (no city, state given), undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 79)
    - Residence, Bogese Construction Company, unidentified location, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 80)
    - Betty's Beauty Salon, unidentified firm, West Cary Street, Richmond, Virginia, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 81)
    - New yard office for Wyoming Yard, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Company, Grand Rapids, Michigan, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 82)
    - Archaeological base map of site of James Towne Island, U.S. Department of Interior, Colonial National Historical Park, Jamestown, Virginia, undated. (rolled) (Box 24)
    - Lost Colony, Fort Raleigh National Historic Site, Manteo, North Carolina, undated. (rolled) (Box 25)
    - Southern map of Georgia and surrounding states, inventory of historic areas of unusual interest (Georgia), undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 83)
    - Residences, H. Clarke Linkous Builder, unidentified location, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous plans, unidentified firm (tentatively attributed to H. Clarke Linkous Builder based on similar, identified plans), unidentified locations, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 85)
    - Residence, Francis E. Frietas Builder, unidentified location, undated. (blueprint) (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 86)
    - Residence, Frederick Hyland AIA, unidentified location, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 87)
    - Residence, unknown firm, unidentified location, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 88)
    - Hospital, unidentified firm, unidentified location, undated. (rolled) (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous plans and sketches, unidentified firm, unidentified locations, undated. (Map-case 8, Drawer 15, Folder 89-90)
  - Subseries IV.E. - Richmond Technical Center.
    Miscellaneous drawings by students at the Richmond Technical Center.
    Arranged by year.
    - 1969. (Map-case 10, Drawer 4, Folder 91)
    - 1970. (Map-case 10, Drawer 4, Folder 92-93)